It's over eight million bucks.
That's a lot of DeNiros.
Oh! This'a berry, berry bad!
Earth's boring.
I'll save us.
Let's go visit my parents
at their fabulous casino in Mars Vegas.
Take that, Earth!
Look out, penny slots.
I've got a system.
It's to put all my money in you.
Um, Zoidberg, maybe Vegas
isn't the best place for people like you.
What? It's full of fat guys in sandals.
I just mean, your money management
skills could use some work.
Like, the only reason my family even
owns a casino is 'cause we've kept
such a close eye on
our money for generations.
You sure have!
No offense, Zoidberg,
but maybe you'd be better off
if you stayed behind.
Oh, yes, better. A lonely weekend
in my dumpster
with a jar of pennies and tears.
Sounds good. See you Monday!
The cops are closing in.
Better ditch the loot somewhere.
Hey-yo, how about that
dumpster down there?
You mean the one in
that alley off 72nd Street?
Yeah. What do you
think I'm pointing at?
Mars Vegas, here we come!
God, it's Zoidberg.
I hate to bother you, but...
Okay, okay, I'll shut up!
This very lucky casino we own.
Someone wins
one million dollar every hour!
Usually it us.
Thirty-three black. Everyone lose.
Man!
I can't help noticing a lot
of your employees are native Martians.
Yeah, they a proud, grouchy people.
Well, they do work for minimum wage
in a land that was once theirs.
Yeah, but they never made
wise use of the land.
When my ancestor
Reginald Wong found them here,
they had no bingo parlors
and only one prostitute.
Pfft. Pathetic.
This here the buffet.
Ooh! Perfect timing!
It's the weekly changing of the shrimp!
Way up here's
the money-counting room.
It's Mars' happiest place on Earth!
This much money
could feed a small, starving planet.
But it doesn't!
I'll just reach down and get that.
Something don't smell right.
Don't mess with Blind Joe.
Nothing get past his sense of smell.
Yeah, that's why he in here.
Guarding galaxy's most secure safe.
Every day at 3:45,
we load in the daily take.
This whole place is finely tuned machine
for separating suckers from their money.
Category five sucker now arriving.
The minute you walked in the
joint I could smell you were a man
Who was stinkin'
A real big lobster, fresh shellfish
You give me a rash
Ladies love a Decapod
With clothes made of cash
Then let me get right to the point
I don't boil my pot for every
Crab I see
Hey, rich lobster
Blow your wad of cash on me
Zoidberg, what are you doing here?
And what's with all the money?
It's my eight million dollars.
God gave it to me.
Oh, come now! God didn't get to be
God by giving away money.
Loosen up.
You can't take it with you.
Now, I'm heading
down to the casino,
and I'm taking
my money with me.
This is why you never see
a poor person with millions of dollars.
Eight one-million-dollar
chips, please.
I think that's about eight.
Everything on 34.
Zoidberg, what are you doing?
I don't know.
I think it's called roulette.
Thirty-four red. You win $288 million.
Let it ride!
Thirty-four red.
Ten billion, 368 million dollars.
Vodka with a sardine in it, please.
In fact, vodka with a sardine all around!
And let it ride!
Stop! At least set aside
a billion for a decent apartment.
No! I'm having fun and a sardini!
Fifteen black.
Aw...
Now that's the God I know.
Zoidberg, what is wrong with you?
You just threw away a fortune!
Eh! Easy come, easy go.
But for one brief moment,
I made everybody on Mars happy.
And if you ask me,
that makes me a winner.
Category five loser now departing.
Hey, big lobster
I'll make this simple.
Our money or your life.
Sardini?
I'm telling you the truth, I swear!
Clamps, break something
over his head.
Everything in here's
already broken.
Find the least broken object
and use that.
This Judith Krantz novel's
only missing its frontispiece.
Ow!
I told you, I spent it in Mars Vegas!
All eight million dollars!
He can't be lyin', boss.
Not after a Krantzing like that.
All right.
Then I'm afraid we must kill you
and dispose of your body
in the nearest dumpster.
This one we're in seems pretty close.
He's full of ink!
We should have brought a gun.
That was one hell
of a weekend in Vegas.
Dude, where's my ship?
I parked it over there.
Well, I don't remember much,
but I feel fine.
Oh, my God!
Amy's mirror got a tattoo!
Luckily, we're prepared
for this eventuality.
What's that?
A tattoo removal laser?
Oh, Hermes,
you and your preposterous sci fi nonsense.
No, this is simply
a translucidating ink polarizer.
It aligns the pigment molecules,
channeling photons through,
and rendering the ink invisible.
Ah. So it's less painful
than regular tattoo removal.
Nobody said that.
The robot mafia's after me!
You got to hide me,
or it's curtains for Johnny Z.
Hide a giant lobster covered in ink?
And how do you propose we do that?
My God!
He was so saturated with ink
that his entire body
structure was polarized!
You mean I'm invisible?
No, no, no.
Not in any sense of the word.
But essentially, yes, entirely.
It's no use, Zoidberg.
We're, like, 85% sure you're in there!
Where is that rat?
Zoidberg's not here.
All right, but if you see him,
give him one of these...
And one of these,
and not one of these.
Come on, Clamps, let's go, and watch out,
there's some sort
of smelly air pocket over here.
Well, that's that. We ain't getting
our money back from this Zoidberg.
Hey, boss, this here casino
looks like it makes a lot of money.
Maybe the Mafia should
get involved in the casino business.
What are you, an idiot?
Pretty much, yeah.
Then you won't notice
when I claim your idea as my own.
Come on, let's go take over this casino.
Fore!
Mr. Wong, we have
a Mafia proposal for you.
Your casino, give it to us.
Okay, fine, I just retire
to my fabulous mansion.
Hey, boss,
ain't that the type of mansion you like?
Oh, Amy, the Mafia took
everything we had.
Our casino, our home,
and our collection of rare servants.
Don't worry, Mom,
you can always come live with me.
No, we can't.
Who do you think been paying your rent?
What's rent?
Okay, we're at the dump.
Where should we heave this stuff?
It's not a dump. It's the company housing
we built for our employees.
Only place we can afford now.
So just drop it here
on this bloody mattress?
Thanks, Tissue Ghost.
You can't afford tissue anymore.
This is Walgreens brand nose paper.
Zoidberg? You snuck in here
while I was taking a bath?
No, you snuck in here
while I was grabbing a bubble cake.
Listen, Zoidberg, I owe you an apology.
No, no, no. Go ahead.
I was condescending to you
'cause you were poor,
but now I realize
it can happen to anyone. I'm sorry.
I appreciate that, Amy.
Is there any way I can help, maybe?
No, I don't see how...
Wait, don't see.
That's how you can help!
There's one sure way
to set everything right.
We'll use your invisibility to pull off
a daring and complex casino heist.
Of course, because no one can
possibly know what I'm up to.
I've summoned you to the chart room
to explain how we're going to break
into the casino vault,
steal millions of dollars
from under the Mafia's nose,
and return the casino
to its rightful owners. Questions?
Uh, how come we've never
been in this room before?
I think this chart will answer that.
Now, the heist.
As you know,
the main vault is here
in the counting room on the top floor.
But your dad said
it's the galaxy's most secure safe.
Yes, but they open it
every day at 3:45 to load the take.
Then Zoidberg walks right in,
because he's invisible.
Well, that, that just might work.
Over here with the donut.
But the money's not invisible.
If the Mafia sees stacks
of cash floating out,
won't they shoot first
and ask questions later?
Not if Zoidberg eats the money.
Everything he swallows turns invisible.
Like so.
Then later we just
retrieve it at our convenience.
Hold on, that much cash would weigh...
over 300 pounds.
How can Zoidberg walk out
with that much weight?
And he may be invisible,
but he's not insmellable.
He stinks like
the inside of a Tauntaun.
Won't someone notice the stench?
No, and to keep you on your toes,
I'll explain why
only after the heist has begun.
The key to the whole operation
is the casino's shrimp buffet.
Today is Friday, the day
the week-old shrimp get hauled off,
so the stench should be
just strong enough
to mask Zoidberg's presence.
Ew.
What's bringing the stank?
It ain't my gambling diaper.
I just changed it. Must be the shrimp.
It's working.
Zoidberg, what are you doing?
Sorry, I'm just so hungry.
Don't spoil your appetite.
You need to eat 300 pounds of cash salad.
At precisely 3:40, the hazmat team
arrives to swap out the shrimp.
Meanwhile, 10 floors above,
the vault is being opened.
Something don't smell right.
Shut your nose. It's just the shrimp cart.
I think there was something
wrong with that rotten shrimp.
Stop griping. Now get in there,
and remember, eat everything in the safe,
especially the little metal box.
That's the most valuable thing of all.
Three, two, one.
Oh, no! Our cart!
We count on that for our job that we do.
Pee-u.
Joey, you got fingers, right?
Help me fix the lady's wheel.
Once our man's inside,
we'll need to distract the Donbot
so he doesn't close
the safe prematurely.
You know, I think I'll close
the safe a little prematurely today.
Whoa.
Don't shut that door, partner.
I'm a crazy Texas robot millionaire,
and I plan on losing billions
in your "casiny."
Can you assure me my losings
will be safe in
this here money closet?
Yes. Please step aside.
Four alarm chili. Four alarm chili.
Hello! I'm Prime Minister
Nelson Okeke of Nigeria.
I trust you received my spam e-mail?
Nelson, thank God you're here, Hermes!
Oh, so full.
And I still have to eat the metal box.
As you can see
by my jeans and hoodie,
I'm a young Internet billionaire.
Help! I'm sick! I can't move at all!
What was that?
Un, I said "Aseeka kanamoo atall."
It means, "We must
leave now in an unusual manner."
I'm enjoying the casino business.
You meet a lot of colorful characters.
Okay, you're good to go.
Get this bubba dump out of here.
Okay, push "roof" and we're home free!
Zoidberg's too heavy!
The elevator's dropping!
Change of plan!
We'll have to leave through the main exit!
Everybody say "fresh shrimp!"
That was a rough ride.
Uh-oh.
Look!
The shrimp cart's paying out!
Keep going. We're almost outside!
Zoidberg, try to just burp up singles.
Blind Joe!
Smell with your eyes
what I see with my nose.
Well, well, well,
what have we here?
Seriously, what is that?
It's whoever or whatever
just emptied out your safe.
All right, shoot him, Blind Joe.
And let this be a lesson to any other
albino lobsters thinking
of robbing our casino.
There ya go.
Don't shoot! I have a deal to offer you.
Sorry. We native Martians aren't so crazy
about deals with the Wong family.
That's because
you don't know the original deal,
the one my family
kept secret for centuries.
This is the original contract
signed by Reginald Wong.
It stated that my ancestors would
hold the land for 100 years,
after which it was supposed
to revert to the Martians.
This casino belongs to your people!
But, Amy, you planned this whole
thing to get the casino back!
Yes, back to its rightful owners.
Now just a hold on minute.
This casino is wrongfully ours.
Security!
Escort the trespassers
to one of the desert's finest holes.
With ironic pleasure.
Let's go, trespassers.
- Hey! What? Hey!
- Those are my clamps!
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Take it easy!
Well, we lost the casino,
but thanks to Amy's kindness,
the Martians gave us back our house.
And our other casino.
So what happens to
the hero of our story, Zoidberg?
Will I be invisible forever?
No, only until you take a bath
and wash off this invisible ink.
So, forever.
Aw, come on. You can use the spa tub
in the high-roller suite.
Hey, big lobster
Take a little bath with me
The minute you flopped in the tub
I could smell you were some
red-tied shellfish
A bam clam chowder
A chuck mollusk
A hoof... or scoop
You're bottled soap for me